<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dumpling Factory</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dumpling Factory</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I’m Wyson Cheng, a security‑minded developer who fell down the homelab rabbit hole while studying Cyber Security at the University of Edinburgh for my master’s. It started in a lecture when the professor said we should all use a password manager—then quickly added we shouldn’t fully trust it either. That got me thinking about how to build the most secure setup for me. I dusted off my old Raspberry Pi 4 from my bachelor’s dissertation at the University of Nottingham, where I built a facial recognition system. That’s when I first got into Docker—the first time I did anything beyond a PHP server, lol. These days I run a K3s cluster on 3 Raspberry Pi 5 devices, provisioned with Ansible and managed GitOps‑style with Flux + Kustomize; Traefik handles ingress, Longhorn provides storage, CloudNativePG powers PostgreSQL, and Prometheus/Grafana monitor the stack—apps like Vaultwarden, Immich, and n8n included. I also have a ZimaBlade running TrueNAS for storage and an N150 machine running Proxmox for networking (here is my project: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ysonC/super-homelab%29&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/ysonC/super-homelab)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
